4x04 - Sorry, Harvey
Transcript: Cordesh/Anyone/Sixe
Synchro: Anyone/Sixe for swsub.com
Oh, it's Ari again.
- All right, I'm gonna take this.
- You want to take it?
Thank you.
Can't you wait for a call back?
As a French might say,
no, I fucking can not.
You know why, Eric?
It's because I have a box
of rare truffles
sitting on  my desk,
a gift from Harvey.
- Do you know why?
-  I can guess.
It's because you sold him on a movie
you're in no position to sell.
Now he thinks we're all travelling
to Cannes together.
Don't worry about it,
it's not your problem.
Not my problem?!
Did you know that Harvey
was a marine, Eric?
A middle class Jew,
who grew up with everything,
yet he chose to join the marines.
- Do you know why?
- No, why?
It's because, and I quote,
he wanted to know
"what it felt like to kill someone."
He will now kill me
when I'll tell him what you did.
Yo, I set a dinner.
I'm telling him tonight, so relax.
- You're gonna tell him in person?
- That's right.
What I wouldn't pay to see that.
Save you're money for botox, Ari.
All that negativity's starting
to take its toll.
Call waiting. Later, loser.
- Lloyd, I see dead people, why?
- I don't know
but M. Night just call
to say he doesn't see you.
Well, I'm at the cemetery
just like he said.
Remind me again
why I put up with this shit?
Because his movies have grossed
almost 2 billion dollars
- and because you're scared of him.
- Thank you, but I fear nothing.
- Little jumpy, Ari?
- We're in a cemetery, Night.
Even for you, this is bizarre.
Don't be an ass.
I'm shooting an IMAX commercial.
Oh, great.
And you want me to star on it?
That's why you've summon me
to the Valley?
No, I finish a new draft of a screenplay
and I don't trust messengers.
You like 6 weeks ahead of schedule.
You bring yourself in it?
I'm gonna improv a little something.
Oh, Indians and improv,
no greater match.
- You gonna read it tonight.
- Of course I will.
Don't tell me you will if you won't.
My night, M. Night,
will be dedicated to nothing
but enjoying your latest creation.
I'm gonna drive by your office
in the morning and I'll pick it up.
- And I'm gonna quizz you.
- As always.
- Alright, Ari.
- See you, Night.
You've got the Misses'
best friends dinner tonight.
Oh, fuck!
Look at this thing, it's 200 pages.
Find me a flashlight, I'm gonna have
to read this at the table.
Why do we have to bring this guy
out with us, Johnny?
'Cause he's the mayor of Beverly Hills.
Then why do you care
if you don't live in Beverly Hills?
I care because the mayor
could use his political clout
to annex my condo in.
How do you like to see this place
rocking a 90210 zip code?
You're 40 feet from the border now,
what's gonna change?
It's like asking what changes
between North and South Corean borders.
Yeah, it's a good analogy.
Turtle, come here.
Look out that window.
You see that brand new fire station
out there? That's Beverly Hills.
Do you know, if they were looking here,
they'd see me burning,
they couldn't do anything about it.
I would have to wait hours
for LA County to come and save me.
I don't wanna wait, Vin.
I wanna be saved.
You are beyond saving, Drama.
- Vince can save me.
- How?
Guy just wants to roll with the big time
celebrity for the evening.
- Have a good time.
- But you're a big time celeb, Johnny.
Why do I have to go?
Well, apparently, he doesn't watch TV.
Look, the annexation vote
is on Wednesday.
He knows what I want and aluded
to the fact
that one hand washes the other.
I need my hands wash, baby Bro.
And you are the soap.
It's Thursday night, Vince.
Fuck his hands.
Shut up, Turtle.
- Is he a good guy, Johnny?
- He's a great guy.
We puff stogies at the Vanmall
all the time.
- Okay, we'll bring him out.
- Yes!
Bring who out where?
We roll with the mayor of Beverly Hills.
Too bad you got to miss it.
Oh, yeah. Too bad.
- Harvey should be fun, though.
- Shut up, Turtle.
Why you can't just
tell Harvey on the phone?
Maybe he loves to feel Harvey
spit me a lobster out of.
No, I just want to be a man
and own up face to face.
You know what? E went out on his own,
against the family on this,
he may have to take a little spit.
Thanks, Vince.
- Little scared of Harvey, huh?
- I'm not afraid of Harvey.
Because, I will go with you,
if you ask nicely.
The mayor, Vince.
No, I got myself into this,
I can get myself out of it.
That's the spirit, kid.
And I'm not afraid of Harvey. I'm trying
to be professionnal and courteous
by doing this but I'm not gonna sit there
while he yells at my face.
You're gonna fight Harvey?
- No, don't fight Harvey, E.
- Harvey's big, E.
Yeah, E, I think Harvey
can definitly take you.
You said that you can take me.
You want to go?
I will fucking...
I'm simply asking you
not to dilly-dally.
That's all.
And I'm not gonna rush their dinner.
This is my best friends engagements.
Come on.
She's been married twice before,
I'm sure we'll get another run of this.
I already stood in the driveway
waiting for you.
Just chew fast and don't order
an appetizer... or dessert.
Give me a break!
Oh, Joyce, you look beautiful.
- Thank you. I'm so excited.
- Me too.
Perfect timing, Ron's at the bar
and we thought we'd get
a before dinner drink. What do you say?
- No?
- No, we're starving.
So, grab your man.
Let's get this thing rolling.
He's kidding, we would love
to have a drink... or two.
Slow down, Turtle.
It's the French country on the right.
Nice house.
He is the mayor of Beverly Hills, bro.
Pull over there, Turtle.
What you're doing?
Let the major know we're here.
You don't honk, you beheaded dog,
You ring the bell like an upstanding
Beverly Hills citizen would do.
Too late.
Don't forget your corsage.
Mayor Lawry!
John Chase...
Is that Vinnie Chase I see in that car?
- Hi, how are you?
- I'm Turtle.
Vinnie, I am a big fan.
Big, big fan.
My kids,
they're just obsessed with Aquaman.
My daughter cried
when they replaced you in the sequel.
Said she will not see it
no matter how good it is.
- Tell her thank you.
- I will. I will.
Ready to go to hell?
Yeah, yeah. Huh...
Got to grab a jacket first.
Walk with me John.
Yeah, this guy's an affair
riding with us.
I really appreciate this.
My wife's been gone for over a year now
and I've been really lonely.
Hey, what are friends for, now?
Yeah, but I think
I'm gonna take my own car.
You sure you don't want
to have Turtle chauffeur?
Then we can get hammered
and have a really good night.
You know what would make it
a really great night, John?
It's if that movie star brother
of yours could help provide me
some comfort of a foxy young thing
I don't have to pay for.
He could do that.
Hi, how are you?
Huh, I'm here to meet Harvey Wei...
- Mr. Murphy?
- Yes.
- Right this way.
- Thank you.
How are you, Eric?
Hey, how are you, Harvey?
Good, good. Great, great.
I'm great. Sit, sit.
Try that wine.
- It's good.
- Good?
That's a '53 Margaux.
It's 33 hundred bucks a bottle.
I only drink it
on celebratory occasions.
This being one,
I ordered two bottles.
Let's celebrate.
Listen, Harvey.
Well, would you look like at this?
See that little cunt?
That prick stole my VP of production.
He's lucky I don't go over there
and crack this fucking bottle
over his head.
I'm not gonna do that, though.
My doctor says I can't do that anymore
'cause my blood pressure
is off the charts.
So...
You and me, E.,
stress free dinner.
- To Medellin.
- Medellin.
I have never been
so embarassed in my life.
What? Wait...
What's so bad?
You got the check
before we got our entrées.
- At least, I paid, right?
- You are such an asshole.
That may be.
But I'm an asshole
that's gonna be home at 9.30
ready to read.
Let's get an early start on this.
Grab my briefcase, you read to me.
Screw you.
Come on, baby, be a team player.
If Night pulls
another half billion dollars gross
out of his hat,
I'll get you some diamonds.
- Briefcase isn't here.
- What do you mean?
Just what I said.
You sure you didn't leave it
in the office?
What, you don't believe me?
Jesus Christ.
The valet probably stole it.
Don't be racist.
Valets steel shit, alright?
Just because they're mostly Hispanic
doesn't make me a racist.
You know what happens if it gets out?
If someone puts Night's new ending
on the Internet?
My life is over!
Nobody's gonna know you did it.
Yes they will. Because Night,
that little sick fuck,
printed my name
on every fucking page.
So maybe the valets put it in the truck.
It's gone, no fucking here.
They fucking stole it.
They motherfukers stole it!
What...
Did they replace it with this?
What the fuck is that?
You tell me, freak.
I have no idea!
Well there's a whole bag!
The seats aren't stuck
as they suppose to be.
- What?
- They gave us the wrong car.
- Shut up.
- Get in there.
What are you, fucking blind?
You're the one
who drive it home, shmuck!
Why would I buy a black cock?
Where the fuck are our salads?
Hey, pal. Pal!
How long we got to wait
for our lousy icebergwich?
You slice the fucking thing,
you put it on a plate
and you bring it over here!
Anyway, E,
what was I talking about?
You're saying that you, huh...
you were pissed off on us
after we fucked you over in Sundance.
Yeah, I was raging.
Sure, you little pricks
make me call a press conference
to annonce I'm in business with you
and then you bail on me?
I know, that was, huh...
that was a big mistake, Harvey.
It was a mistake?
That was some mistake.
Don't you ever make a mistake
like that with me again.
Because next time,
I'm not gonna be so kind.
I killed people.
Do you mind if I use the bathroom?
Sure, go ahead.
On your way over there,
walk by that cunt's table
and give him
a little elbow on the head.
If you feel like it.
How am I gonna get
this guy a laid, Johnny?
Seriously.
Tell girls if they fuck him,
you'll fuck 'em after.
That sounds like
a good deal for Vince.
He'd be lying.
Oh, Jesus.
How did he beat us here?
What's up, Vince?
How is it going over there?
It's not.
This guy is nuts.
He's tittering on the edge.
Did he yell at you?
He didn't,
because I didn't tell him yet.
I thought you said
you're not afraid of Harvey.
I ain't,
but it wouldn't be good for anybody
if I ended up rolling on the parking lot
with one of the most powerful men
in Hollywood.
So what you want me to do?
I want you to come down here.
- I'm with the mayor, E.
- Fuck the mayor.
Harvey's not gonna make the same kind
of scene if you're here.
Swallow your pride,
admit you're afraid of him
and I'm there.
I'm not scared of Harvey.
How long you think you can keep me
waiting at the table
without me getting antsy?
Sorry about that.
I'm actually talking to Vince right now.
Hey, Vince.
How the fuck are you?
Hey, Harvey.
Where are you, son?
I just walked in a place
called Winston's
I love Winston's.
We'll come over there
for a celebratory toast.
Walk the other way, David,
or I'll pull out your fuckin' eyeballs.
- Yeah, we see you soon.
- See you.
Come on, eat!
Nel really likes this one over here.
Could you go talk to her?
It's a black LS Hybrid.
So don't be afraid to step on the gas
and get it up here.
But, sir, this is a black LS.
That's the wrong black LS, obviously.
Okay, do you... is there a manager?
I am the manager.
An English speaking manager?
- I speak English.
- First language English speaking?
It's okay.
You switched cars on us.
Oh shit, that's not your car.
The guy who just left with the same car,
accused us of stealing his glasses.
Here they are.
Wrongfully accuse again.
So, he's gone?
Yeah, but I'm sure he gonna
come back as soon as he realizes.
I don't have time to wait.
I have something I need
to get off the car tonight.
There's nothing you can do...
There's always something
that can be done, baby.
Sometimes, you just have to think
really, really hard.
So everybody think.
And do we got something?
You got something?
You could always go to his house
and hope that he's home.
What, you know where he lives?
But does it never occurs to you,
rich people,
that when you are enjoying
a nice dinner, we have your keys
and your fancy navigation system
to lead us straight
to your empty house?
I like your style, Pal.
Oxnard. How far is that?
About 50 miles.
You're taking me home first.
Thank you, sir.
5-5-3-2
Cool, so I call you at like... 2.00?
Huh, make it 2.30,
the boys and I usually grab
a bite late night.
Thought you're supposed to phone
for the mayor, not ourselves.
I'm just not a good wrangler.
Yeah but I am, and I've been wasting
my skills on Drama's cause.
You're telling me you'd be
poll in it if it was for your cause?
Of course I would be.
What kind of question is that?
Fellas, guess who's into politics?
This is Enika.
Anika.
- Anika, the boys.
- Hello, boys.
Anika is from Prague.
I told her a little about our man
and she's very impressed.
Gotta love the eastern block.
Back in a flash.
Nel, say hello to Anika.
Anika, the one and only mayor
of Beverly Hills, Nel Lawry.
Johnny has told me of your dedication
to the city and of your kindness.
It is so nice to meet you.
You too. You too.
Would you like to sit?
Yes, I would love to.
My God, you have gorgeous feet.
How about that.
How about this?
He looks like a P.O.W.
(ny: POW = prisoner of war)
- Who is it?
- Hi. My name is Ari Gold.
- I think you have my car.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
- Will you open the door?
No! And I have a dog!
That's great.
I think you also have my car.
Do you drive a black Lexus?
My husband does.
Well, I think the valet gave him
the wrong car, 'cause I'm driving his.
- Valet? What valet?
- The valet at Morton's tonight.
- Morton's in LA?
- Yeah.
What was my husband doing
at Morton's in LA tonight?
What the fuck were you doing
at Morton's tonight?
- What?
- The valet switched our cars.
- Answer me! Who the fuck were you with?
See? That's my briefcase!
Thank you God!
Answer me, you piece of shit!
- What?
- Listen,
here are your keys. Can I get mine?
I am fucking waiting
for a fucking answer!
Deny it 'til you die, pal.
I'll tell you what,
Just admit that you're scared of him
and I'll apologize for you.
I don't need you to apologize. I just
want you to be here when he goes down.
I'm right here!
What are you waiting for?
The right moment!
Buy the chuck,
we're they real Winstons or what?
Yeah, only mine is the good looks,
ten in a buttonny five hundred, suit.
I got one of those suits, bro.
Yo, Ben!
Yo, Ray!
This is delicate.
- What's that?
- You know, the boy you came in with?
Yeah. What about him?
He's about to suck face with a tranny.
What? Come on...
That's no tranny, Ray! That's Anika!
Anika's got a bigger stump
than you do, Drama
If you John had knew that,
he would have kept her for himself!
Ray, are you sure?
Trust me. The only reason we let
that he/she in here
is cause she goes on Howard Stern.
We don't need a bad ink. I'm sorry bro.
- I can't believe it!
- Believe it, Drama.
- Thanks, man. I appreciate it.
- No doubt, man.
What do we do?
I ain't saying shit.
Nobody's saying nothing until I'm 90210.
Johnny, you'll find out eventually
that you'd better pray
he's not your mayor.
Do the right thing!
- Fine, I'll tell him.
- E.?
I'm going.
A couple of shots, first, to relax?
Definitely!
Yeah, Lloyd?
Just make sure you're up and reading.
Well, I'm up
and I'm not fucking reading!
You're even angry in the evening?
Fuck off, Lloyd!
Good night, Ari.
- Yes, alright.
- Talk to me while I drive
- so I don't fall asleep.
- Okay, Ari.
Oh, fuck!
- What?
- I'm getting pulled over.
How fast are you going?
225.
That's not good...
Cheers!
I'm going in.
And E., why aren't your feet moving?
Alright. I'm scared of him.
We'll see...
Come on. I'll talk to him.
I'll stand right next to you.
We'll all be hanging back, having fun.
Hi.
Or not...
Anika, would you excuse us for a second?
Yeah, sure.
You'd better hurry back,
or I'm gonna come chasing.
I will.
Hey, John, what's happening?
- It's about Anika.
- Yeah?
You know, we didn't even need
Vinny central, huh?
Thank you.
I tell you, she is one doll...
Yeah, well, according to some,
that Barbie might be a Ken.
She might have balls, Your Honor.
What?
She's a he, transformer, hermaphrodite,
something that just ain't right.
I don't believe that. Look at her!
She's beautiful.
I got only reasons to lie to you now.
It's true!
- I'm sorry.
- I am too!
I appreciate your honesty.
And I would appreciate
your palsy's discretion
cause I don't care
what she's got under that dress.
We have a connection. She gets me!
Hey, babe,
you're ready to get out of here?
I got a blue Mercedes tainted windows
see out there in ten minutes.
What about my annexation?
Looking good!
Sweet.
I love you.
Sit down.
So... So, what's on your mind?
- It's about Medellin.
- What about it?
- We...
- Vodkas, fresh cranberry.
- I ordered tonic.
- No, you didn't, you ordered cranberry.
Why would I ordered cranberry
if I don't drink cranberry?
I don't know, but you did.
You believe this fucking guy?
I'll give you a tonic.
Don't give me a tonic.
Tell me I didn't ordered cranberry.
- But, you did.
- Are you out of your fucking mind?
Just get the tonic guy.
Don't go anywhere.
What are you doing?
I'm not telling him.
He's out of his mind.
You know what?
I'll do it.
Harvey, look.
You look me in the fucking face.
You tell me why,
that after fifty years of life,
and never having even sipped
cranberry juice,
for some reason, I come in here
and I order cranberry juice?
Can you answer that,
you fucking scumbag?
No, I can't, but you did.
I'm gonna fucking kill him.
- Take it easy, sir.
- Don't tell me to take it easy!
You know who the fuck I am?
I was rolling my balls when
you were sucking your mother's titty!
- Let's leave my mother out of this.
- Fuck you!
- Fuck him!
- Alright pal, you out of here.
Come on!
Get your fucking hands off me!
So you let Vince do your dirty work,
huh, E?
Nah, he couldn't do it.
Hey, E, had him, after all.
Nah, I didn't get a chance too either.
But I'll try tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
What?
You weak, weak man.
Hey, Harvey!
We're not selling you the movie.
Sorry bro, we're putting it
on the open market in Cannes.
You're gonna have
to bid like everyone else.
I'll eat you alive.
I'll eat you alive,
and trifle you out of my tooth !
After what you've done this time.
You'll never work again!
Never! You understand me?
Your career is over!
He was talking about E, not me, right?
Morning, Ari.
Done.
Night in me office?
- Yes sir, he just got here.
- Perfect timing.
Are your wearing
the same suit as yesterday?
I spent the night in jail.
Oh my God!
Why didn't you call me?
You get one call, and I wanted to use it
on someone I like to have sex with.
Genius.
Best script yet.
Ask me anything.
How could you
possibly like that third act?
Are you kidding?
The twist with the dove? I loved it.
- It was perfect.
- No, it's fucked!
What you read is totally fucked!
I tried to call you last night.
You didn't have your cell.
I dont' understand.
After you left, it hit me.
The all 3rd act is a mess, man.
It's a mess!
I changed it.
It really works, now.
You read it.
I'll wait.
Start from the top scene, get the flow.
Morning, fellas.
- Get them while they're hot.
- You just saved E's ass.
He's been wresling
with your expresso maker for an hour.
Wrestle no more, E.
I got your favourite caramel macchiato.
I hate caramel, but very thoughtful,
nonetheless.
Indeed, it was.
But even more thoughtful,
were the coffees
I brought over
to the Beverly Hills firehouse
when I went over to introduce myself.
You're expecting a fire,
or you just hoping to slide up
and down on their pole?
You slay me!
No, really, I'm just proud to be a...
soon to be annexed resident
of the queen city known
throughout the world as Beverly Hills.
Yeah, I wouldn't be too proud
too fast, Drama.
How much longer your boy
is gonna be mayor?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the all seeing,
all knowing lenses of TMZ.com.
Look at this.
Hey, mayor, I'm from TMZ,
how about saying a little something?
Howdy folks!
Why are you sneaking out the alley?
I'm not sneaking.
There's no sneaking going on here.
Fast in the car, babe.
That's nuts.